好了
Okay. Hey.
- 这双鞋很难看吗   - 绝对
- Does everybody hate these shoes?     - Oh, yeah.
但是你穿了这浴巾晚礼服 所以大家不会注意你的鞋
But I don't think anybody's gonna focus on that as long as you wear that towel dress.
说给他懂
Tell him.
今天是她新工作第一天 别一早就惹她
It's her first day at this new job. You're not supposed to start with her.
好吧 那我等晚点
All right. I suppose I can wait a day.
- 礼拜五要干嘛   - 干嘛
- Hey, what are you doing Friday?     - Why?
个性古怪的表弟艾伯告别单身派对 找你一起去
I need you to come to this bachelor party for my weird cousin Albert.
就植物学家那个
You know, he's the botanist?
天啊 植物学家都是怪胎耶
Oh, God. Yeah, botanists are such geeks.
是啊
Yeah.
那是恐龙领带吗
Is that a dinosaur tie?
对
Hmm? Oh, yeah.
- 早   - 早
- Morning.     - Hey.
瑞秋 我把皮包都带来了
Hey. Rach, I'm here with the purses.
一定很难找钥匙吧
It must take you forever to find your keys.
谢你喔 菲比
Thank you, thank you, Pheebs.
不客气 可以选有乌龟的那个吗
Oh, you're welcome. Oh, please want the one with the turtles.
乌龟很吓人 今天不要
No, no, no, turtles scare me. I don't need that today.
亲爱的 别慌 会很顺利的
Honey, just relax. It's gonna be fine.
我中午去找你吃饭好了
Hey, why don't I come down there and take you to lunch?
亲爱的 谢了 不过我要跟马克去吃
Aw, honey, thank you, but Mark's taking me out.
马克 是帮你找到这工作的马克吗
Mark? Is that the same Mark that helped you get the job?
是啊 只是来恭喜我正式上班而已
Yeah. It's kind of like a "good luck on your first day" sort of thing.
这不会是便当盒吗
Is this actually a lunch box?
不是 是皮包 里头还有保温瓶
Um, no, it's a purse. And there's a thermos in it.
- 所以你礼拜五可以吗   - 什么
- Hey, so can you make it on Friday?     - What?
喔 应该吧 再跟我说是要干嘛
Oh, yeah, I think so. Why am I invited to this again?
显然艾伯没什么朋友
Apparently, Albert has no friends.
但他还是对婚前派对一事很期待
He's excited about the bachelor party, though.
我猜结婚就是为了能看到脱衣舞娘
I think the only reason he's getting married is so he can see a stripper.
婚前派对找脱衣舞娘 真老套
A stripper at a bachelor party. That is so cliche.
怎不请魔术师
Why don't you guys get a magician?
要是魔术师能用臀部开啤酒罐 那就请啊
If a magician can open my beer with his butt cheeks, then all right.
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 纵有狂风暴雨 #
# When the rain starts to pour #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 支持一如往昔 #
# Like I've been there before #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
她跟他吃午餐 跟他吗
She's having lunch with him? Lunch with him?
她应征到工作时 他抱她的样子你都没看到
You should've seen the hug he gave her when she got the job.
加上他又那么帅
And he's really good-looking.
- 我要怎么办   - 按兵不动
- What am I gonna do?     - You don't do anything.
吞下去 学会隐藏情绪
Keep it inside. Learn how to hide your feelings.
别大呼小叫的
Don't cry out loud.
好耶
Yes! Unh!
看谁得到百老汇歌舞剧面试机会了
Guess who has an audition for a Broadway musical.
我想猜是你 但这未免太容易了
I wanna say you, but it seems like such an easy answer.
是我没错
It is me.
是歌舞版的"双城记"
It's a musical version of A Tale of Two Cities.
应该可以唱"纽约 纽约"
So I think I'm gonna sing "New York, New York"...
和"我的心留在旧金山"
...and, uh, oh, "I Left My Heart in San Francisco."
乔伊 剧情跟哪座城市有关 应该不是由你来选的
Uh, Joey, I don't think you get to pick the cities.
- 哈   - 狄更斯先生早决定好了
- What?     - Mr. Dickens gets to pick them.
谁
Who?
翻"学生戏剧指南"给你看
I'll get you the CliffsNotes.
什么南
The what?
就故事摘要
The abridgment.
好
Oh, okay. Ha, ha.
什么要
The what?
接着是型式编码
Then the style number...
货单编号 寄送日期
...the invoice number, and the shipping date.
很好 到目前为止 有问题吗
Good. Any questions so far?
有 员工折扣多少
Yeah. What kind of discount do we get?
- 八折   - 爱死这工作了
- Ha, ha. Twenty percent.     - Oh. I love this job. Ha, ha.
- 第一通电话   - 我来接
- Ah! My first call.     - Here, let me.
好
Okay.
- 瑞秋•葛林座位 有何贵干   - 瑞秋在吗
- Rachel Green's line. How may I help you?     - Hi, is Rachel there?
- 请问哪位   - 罗斯
- And who may I say is calling?     - This is Ross.
罗斯什么
Ross of?
男女朋友罗斯和瑞秋的罗斯
Of "Ross and Rachel."
你好 我是马克
Oh. Hi, it's Mark.
- 你好 马克   - 你好
- Oh, hey, Mark. Heh. Hey.     - Hey.
- 请稍候   - 好
- Hey, hold on a second.     - Uh, okay.
- 罗斯找你   - 好
- It's Ross.     - Okay.
- 亲爱的   - 你好
- Hi, honey.     - Hi.
怎么是马克接的
What's Mark doing answering your phone?
他闹着玩
Oh, he's just goofing around.
真有趣
Oh, that's funny.
他怎不会在自己办公室玩
Why isn't he goofing around in his own office?
亲爱的 这也算他办公室 我们都是乔安娜的助理
Ha, ha. Honey, this is his office too. I told you, we're Joanna's two assistants.
乔安娜干嘛要两名助理
Why does Joanna need two assistants?
她这人是有多懒
How lazy is she?
- 天啊 发生什么事了   - 什么
- Oh. Oh, my God. What did I just do?     - What?
我寄了三千个胸罩给人事部了
I think I just shipped 3000 bras to Personnel.
亲爱的 不能聊了 马克 救命
Honey, I gotta go. Mark, I need you.
好 再见
Okay. Bye-bye.
罗斯
Ow! Ross!
抱歉 亲爱的 我只是在…
Huh? Oh. Oh, I'm sorry, sweetie. I was just trying to...
拨另一个号码
Uh, I was dialing another number.
我30秒快速换好装 好让你能跟他独处
All right, I just got changed in 30 seconds so you could be alone with him.
- 你赶快采取行动   - 拜托 我才不要采取行动
- You better go for it.     - Please. I'm not going for anything.
- 要是你不上 我要上了喔   - 拜托你走了吧
- Well, if you don't, I will.     - Would you please go?
再见 摩妮卡
Night, Mon.
再见 胡立欧
Night, Julio.
胡立欧 有客人忘了把书带走
Look, Julio, someone left their book here.
书是我的
Actually, that is mine.
- 是喔   - 对
- Oh, yeah?     - Yes.
这什么书
What are you reading?
波特莱尔的"恶之华" 你有读过吗
Flowers of Evil by Baudelaire. Have you read it?
还用问吗
Ha, ha. Have I read it?
没读过 你喜欢吗
No. Are you enjoying it?
应该算喜欢吧 但这版的翻译不太好
I thought that I would, but the translation's no good.
大诗人耶 还真懂
You're a poet and you don't know it.
我真的是诗人
Actually, I, uh... I am a poet.
原来你真的懂喔
So you do know it. Ha, ha.
那你的诗都是哪类
Ahem. So, uh, what kind of things do you write about?
让我成动的诗
Things that move me.
树影
The shadow of a tree...
婴儿的笑容
...a child laughing...
或这点红唇
...or this lip.
我
Mine?
这点
Right here?
这点朱唇我就能写上一阙长诗
I could write an epic poem about this lip.
怎么开始
How would that go?
这没押韵耶
Well, it didn't rhyme, ha, ha...
不过我喜欢
...but I liked it.
# 你要偷一两个钱包 男孩 #
# You've got to pick a pocket or two, boys #
# 你要偷一两个钱包 #
# You've got to pick a pocket or two #
不赖 不赖
Lovely. Just lovely.
真的吗 谢谢
Really? Thanks.
乔伊 礼拜六的复试你一定要再来参加
Listen, Joey, we definitely wanna see you for the callback on Saturday.
太好了
Excellent.
- 我一定到   - 好
- I'll be there.     - Ha, ha. Okay.
还有 记得带爵士舞鞋 要面试舞蹈喔
And listen, don't forget to bring your jazz shoes for the dance audition.
经纪人说帮我接的角色不用跳舞
Uh, my agent said that it wasn't a dancing part.
乔伊 戏中所有角色多少都得跳舞
Joey, all the roles gotta dance a little. Ha, ha.
但以你的舞蹈背景 这绝对轻松过关
But believe me, with your dance background, it'll be a piece of cake.
在"崔拉莎普现代舞团" 有三年工作经验
Three years of modern dance with Twyla Tharp?
在"美国芭蕾舞团" 有五年工作经验
Five years with the American Ballet Theatre?
谁的履历不吹牛的啊 拜托喔
Hey, everybody lies on their resume, okay?
上面写的儿童电视节目我也没真的参加过啊
I wasn't one of the Zoom kids either.
那你究竟能不能跳舞呢
Well, can you, like, dance at all?
我会跳啊
Yeah, I can dance. You know:
不 不 不 不
Oh, no, no, no.
这什么啊
What is that?
现在看当然很蠢啊 因为没有音乐
Sure, it looks stupid now. There's no music playing.
这电话我得接 但你不行
All right, I have to get that. But no, no.
你好
Hello?
是的 我需要一名脱衣女郎 听说你有做这服务
Yeah, listen, I'm in need of a stripper, and I was told that you do that.
容我一问 多给你一百有什么服务
Let me ask you this. What do you do for the extra hundred?
那葡萄由我提供吗
So would I have to provide the grapes?
大家好
Hi.
昨晚跟胡立欧进行如何小姐
How was last night with Julio, señorita? Ha, ha.
太棒了
It was so amazing.
他好性感又好有才华 所以更性感了
He's so sexy and smart, which makes him even sexier.
跟你们说 昨晚我们在调情时
Oh, my gosh. Last night we were fooling around...
突然间他停下来 就写了一首诗
...and all of a sudden he stops to write a poem.
少来了 换我就算被陨石击中也不会停
Get out. I couldn't stop if a meteor hit me.
请到脱衣女郎了 花名水晶吊灯小姐
Okay, we have our stripper, a Miss Crystal Chandelier.
是喔 给小孩取这种名字 难怪长大变这样
Well, sure. You name a kid that, what do you expect them to grow up to be?
他走时诗没带走
Ahem. Anyway, when he left he forgot to take the poem with him.
诗我是不在行啦 但这首很不赖
Now, I am totally dense about poetry, but I think this is pretty good, all right?
大家看看
Check it out. Read it.
"空瓶"
"The Empty Vase."
透明的美
Translucent beauty...
不用大声念
To yourself.
- 真的不赖耶   - 我也这么觉得 菲比呢
- Hey, you know, that's pretty good.     - Yeah, I think so too. Phoebe?
- 对   - 太好了 很高兴大家都喜欢
- Oh, yeah.     - Oh, great. I'm so glad you guys like it.
- 好了 我要上班了   - 我还没看完
- Yay. All right, I gotta go to work.     - No, no. I'm not done.
那你等看完再还我
Give it back when you're through.
- 好 再见   - 再见
- Okay, see you guys.     - Bye-bye.
再见
Bye.
天啊 可怜的摩妮卡
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Poor Monica.
- 怎样 怎样   - 怎样
- What? What? What?     - What?
这诗是他对她的心情写照
He was with her when he wrote this poem. Look.
我的容器很可爱 却似乎空空如也
My vessel so lovely With nothing inside
真正面对面接触后果然空无一物
Now that I've touched you You seem emptier still
他觉得摩妮卡很没深度 像空瓶子一样
He thinks Monica's empty. She's the empty vase.
- 诗真的这意思吗   - 绝对是
- You really think that's what he meant?     - Totally.
天啊 她确还一副得意洋洋的样子
Oh, God. Oh, and she seems so happy too.
看完了
Done.
（我好爱你）
圣罗兰档案在你那吗
Do you have the Ralph Lauren file?
在 就在
Oh, yeah, sure. It's, uh right...
那是什么
What's that?
罗斯送的爱的金龟
Uh, it's from Ross. It's a love bug.
有人想昭告天下 你是名花有主
Wow. Somebody wants people to know you have a boyfriend.
没啦 他不是这意思
Oh, no. No, no, no. That's not what he's doing.
- 他只是很浪漫   - 好
- He's just really romantic.     - Okay.
打扰了 请问是 瑞秋•葛林吗
Excuse me. Are you Rachel Green?
是 正是
Yes, I am.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
# 恭喜新工作第一周 #
# Congratulations on your first week at your brand-new job. #
# 很快你就会当老板 #
# It won't be long Before you're the boss #
# 你清楚谁会支持你 #
# And you know who will be there To support you #
# 就是你唯一无二的男友 #
# Your one and only boyfriend #
# 有男友真好 #
# It's nice to have a boyfriend. #
#忠心耿耿又爱你的罗斯 #
# Your loyal, loving boyfriend, Ross Ross! #
伤到我了 真的伤到我了
I'm hurt. I'm actually hurt...
你竟然说我送你那些东西 除了爱意以外别有用心
...that you'd think I'd send you those things out of anything other than love.
心好痛
Hurt.
- 心好痛   - 好啦 我懂了 我伤到你了
- Hurt.     - All right, Ross, I get it. You're hurt.
难道男友现在不可以请四重唱到女友办公室唱歌了吗
Can't a guy send a barbershop quartet to his girlfriend's office anymore?
拜托 罗斯 这用意也太明显了
Oh, please. Ross, it was so obvious.
根本就像在划地盘
It was like you were marking your territory.
你干脆直接到我办公桌旁撒泡尿好了
I mean, you might as well have just come in and peed all around my desk.
我才不会这样
I would never do that.
我很清楚你在搞什么把戏 好吗
Look, I know what's going on here, okay?
马克都解释给我听了 他说男人都这样搞的
Mark explained it all to me. He said this is what you guys do.
要是马克这么跟你说 那他真笨
Yeah, well, if Mark said that, then Mark's an idiot.
马克真是天才
Mark's a genius.
- 怎么说他怎会是天才   - 你们不懂这是怎么回事吗
- Why? How? How is he a genius?     - Look, don't you see what's happening?
他不直接追她 却装作是她的知心手帕交
Instead of hitting on her right away, he's becoming her confidant.
他现在成了她抱怨你的手帕交了
Now he's gonna be the guy that she goes to to complain about you.
我怎么办
What am I gonna do?
何不送她一个音乐金龟
Well, why don't you send her a musical bug?
不 这你已经做过了
Oh, no, you already did that.
你要亲自过去
All right, look, you're gonna have to go there yourself now, okay?
- 给她来个意外造访   - 不知道耶
- Make a few surprise visits.     - I don't know, you guys.
好 啥都别做 就坐这跟我们聊
Fine, don't do anything. Just sit here and talk to us.
这同时她可是在跟他抱怨你 他则扮演推心置腹的好朋友角色
Meanwhile, she is talking to him about you. And he's being Mr. Joe-Sensitive.
她开始会觉得或许这才是我要的人 因为他懂我
She starts thinking, "Maybe this is the guy for me because he understands me."
不知不觉之间 她已经跟他在一起了
And before you know it, she's with him.
到时候你就只能唉声叹气了
And you'll be all, "Oh, man."
他却是痛快极了
And he'll be all, "Yes!"
而我们只能说 傻瓜
And us, we'll be like, "Oh, dude."
而你很快就只能
And pretty soon you'll be like:
嗨
"Hi."
说着"我不能去 瑞秋和马克可能也会到"
And, "Well, I can't go. Rachel and Mark might be there."
我们则只能说 "别放在心上 都四年了"
And we'll be like, "Man, get over it. It's been four years."
还真是生动的画面
He paints quite a picture, doesn't he?
这边是12月的雪莉席格货单
Here's the Shelli Segal stuff for December.
- 等等 有东西给你   - 什么马克
- Oh, wait, I've got something for you.     - What? Oh... Mark.
没关系 瑞秋知道
It's okay. Rachel knows.
但即使如此
Yeah, but even so... Ha, ha.
我情不自禁 我真的为你疯狂
I can't help it. I'm just crazy about you.
好甜蜜喔
Oh, that is so sweet.
好啦
Okay, okay.
我知道今天我有点过分 但很难熬
I know I'm Mr. Inappropriate today, but it's just so tough.
看着你走来走去 让我好想抱抱你
I see you walking around, and I just wanna touch and hold you.
来吧 没旁人在 亲亲
Come on, no one's around. Just kiss me.
- 够了 分开 分开   - 怎么回事
- All right, that's it. Get off. Get off of her.     - What is going on?
怎么回事 我跟你说怎么回事
What's going on? I'll tell you what's going on.
罗斯
Ross.
我在你们店里逛了20分钟 想买条领带
I have been down in your store for 20 minutes, trying to get a tie.
怎样才能有店员肯上来招呼我
What do I have to do to get some service?
你好 瑞秋
Hi, Rach.
乔伊 乔伊•崔比亚尼
Uh, Joey? Joey Tribbiani?
听好 乔伊 有个问题 领舞的舞者刚打来
Listen, Joey, I got a problem. I just got a call from my dance captain.
他的感情触礁了 所以没法脱身
He's having a relationship crisis and can't get out of Long Island.
这表示面试取消了吗
So does that mean the audition's off?
乔伊 既然你是这里最有经验的人
Listen, Joey, seeing as you've got the most experience...
就由你来教其他舞者舞步
...I want you to take these dancers and teach them the combination.
什么
What?
乔伊 拜托 这很简单
Oh, Joey, come on, it's easy.
就手 头
You know, it's hand, hand, head, head...
侧跨 侧跨
...up, pas de bourrée, pas de bourree...
转身 抬腿 跳跃
...big turn here, rond de jambe, sissonne, sissonne...
滑步
...slide, step, step...
手张开
...and jazz hands.
就跳几步然后手张开
So that's steppity-step and jazz hands.
好好玩
Have fun.
再见
Bye.
- 你好   - 你好
- Hey.     - Hey.
你在包装什么
What are you wrapping?
要送胡立欧的
Look what I got Julio.
- 是只瓶子   - 是啊
- Yeah, it's a vase.     - Yeah.
就跟诗里的一样
Just like the one in the poem.
对 但跟诗里的不一样
Yeah, well, not exactly like the one in the poem.
什么意思
What do you mean?
记得你说过 你对诗不在行吗
Remember how you said you were really dense about poetry?
对
Yeah.
- 我不过是只没有内涵的瓶子是吗   - 什么
- So I'm just an empty vase, huh?     - What?
我是没读过什么名著
So I don't read as many important books as you do.
也不会写些指桑骂槐的诗
I don't write poems that seem to be about one thing but are about something else.
而且我又很容易对平凡事物就心动
And you know what? I get excited about stupid stuff...
像是礼拜六"时人杂志"送来时
...like when my People magazine comes on Saturday...
新的"应有尽有"目录寄来时
...and the new Hold Everything catalog.
但那不表示我没有内涵
But that does not mean I'm empty.
我有心 我对朋友和家人有心
I care about things. I care about my friends and family.
你没资格这样评断我
You have no right to make that judgment about me.
你又不认识我
You don't even know me.
我写的那首诗不是在写你
The poem is not about you.
- 什么   - "空瓶"不是在写你
- What?     - "The Empty Vase" is not about you.
我的宝贝
My baby preciosa.
被你误解真让我伤心
You make me so sad that you would think this.
- 抱歉 是我朋友菲比说的   - 不
- I'm sorry. It's... My friend Phoebe said...     - No, it's...
我是在描写天下所有的女人
It's about all women.
全美国的女人
Well, heh, all American women.
这有让你比较好受吗
You feel better now?
是喔
Oh, yeah.
好 来吧
All right, let's do it.
不对 不对啦
No, no, no.
这什么东西
What was that?
我了解 但他们只能做到这程度
I know, it's the best I could get out of them.
- 各位   - 各位
- Well, people.     - People, people, people.
再来一遍 这遍大家看着乔伊跳
Let's try it again. And this time, let's everybody watch Joey.
你来示范正确动作
Show them how it's done.
弹琴 麦克
Count it off, Mack.
（中央咖啡厅）
昨晚婚前单身派对玩得愉快吗
So did you have fun at the bachelor party last night?
愉快 给你看个东西
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Look what I got.
- 你看 她都有穿喔   -  对
- See, she's fully dressed, right?     - Right.
按一下后 变没穿了
And then you click it and, uh-oh, she's naked.
再按一下 又有穿了
And then you click it again and she's dressed.
这下是事业女强人在逛街
She's a business woman, walking down the street.
购物 然后又没穿了
She's window shopping, and, oh, oh, oh, she's naked.
你好
Hi.
Hello.
我想跟我的笔独处一下
You know what? I'm gonna spend some alone time with the pen.
抱歉 我真蠢
I'm sorry. I was an idiot.
- 蠢毙了   - 蠢毙了
- A big idiot.     - A big idiot. Heh.
只是 请你理解 马克这事件我就是无法释怀
It's just, you have to realize, this whole Mark thing is really hard for me.
亲爱的 怎会无法释怀 我们都在一起快一年了
Honey, why is it hard? We've been together for almost a year now.
我之前跟卡萝在一起八年 都还会分了
Well, I was with Carol for like eight years, and I lost her.
而对你 我似乎爱得更多
And now, if it's possible, I think I love you even more.
所以我不由得会往坏处想
So it's hard for me to believe I'm not gonna...
总觉得有人会抢走你
Well, that someone else isn't gonna take you away.
让我当那个人
Let it be me. Let it be me.
亲爱的 这番话好动人
Honey, that's very sweet.
但我是这么想 两个人如果真心相爱
It just seems to me, though, that if two people love each other...
又互相信赖 跟我们一样
...and trust each other, like we do...
那就没必要吃醋
...there's no reason to be jealous.
我要走了 再见 钱德
I gotta get going. Bye, Chandler.
好 罗斯
Oh, okay, Ross.
这笔有点无聊了 帮我买些色情书刊好吗
Listen, this pen's getting kind of boring, so can you pick me up some porn?
- 你去哪   - 我去接小班
- Where you going?     - I've gotta go pick up Ben.
跟他约好了下午要陪他玩
We've got a playdate this afternoon.
还有谁
Oh. With who?
就昨晚在派对上认识的女孩
Just this woman I met last night at the party.
有女孩
There was a woman at?
是说脱衣女郎
The stripper?
对
Yeah.
你跟脱衣女郎有约
You have a playdate with a stripper?
还真该弄个小孩来
Man, I gotta get a kid.
对啊
Uh, yeah, yeah.
就她那个以后 我们就聊开了
We started talking after she, you know, did her thing...
刚好她也有个儿子 跟小班一样年纪
...and it turns out she's got a boy about Ben's age.
所以我们要一起带去上体操课
So we're gonna take the kids to a Gymboree class.
- 可以吗   - 当然 她结婚没
- Is that okay?     - Sure. Is she married?
没
No.
你在吃醋吗
Are you jealous?
没啊 只是不懂她非找你不可而已
No. You know, I just don't see why she has to play with you, that's all.
难道她没有
I mean, doesn't she, you know...
其他一样做脱衣舞的朋友吗
...have any other stripper-mom friends of her own?
- 你明明就是在吃醋   - 我没在吃醋好吗
- You are totally jealous.     - Ugh. I'm not jealous, all right?
这是跟…
This is about...
人们对某种…
...um, people feeling certain things...
像是…
...you know, about...
脱衣女郎的感受
...strippers.
- 而且   - 亲爱的 我也爱你
- And, you know... And, um... I... Ugh.     - Honey, I love you too.
- 再见   - 等等
- Bye.     - Wait, wait, wait.
啥
What?
这吻他肯定好几小时忘不了
Well, there's a kiss he won't forget for a few hours, you know?
对
Yeah.
不然的话就是你引起他的性欲 再把他送到脱衣女郎手上
Either that or you just turned him on and sent him off to a stripper.
这里有位叫胡立欧的吗
Is there a Julio here?
我就是
I am Julio.
做作先生
Mr. Pretentious
你自以为了不起
You think there's no one finer
你的诗卖不出去 只能在餐馆上班
Well, your poems are unpublished And you work in a diner
你也不是上帝赐给女人的礼物 全是你的想像
You're no God's gift to women That's all in your head
你不过是个浑球
You are just a butt-munch
浑球惹人厌
No one likes a butt-munch.
床上表现也很差
And you're also bad in bed